#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/vivek-yadav-665823129 (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

Flutter

Android

Node.js

### Certifications

Android and Java

The Complete Flutter App Development Course for Android, iOS

Android

Certified ScrumMaster (CSM)

Flutter - Beginners Course

# Vivek Yadav

Flutter Dev at Rirev, Speaker at Flutter, Co-Organizer at Flutter Mumbai

Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

## Summary

Things I know: Flutter, Firebase, Android(Java, Kotlin), NodeJS

Currently: Flutter Developer @Rirev

I hold experience of Android and nodejs development for more than 2 years. and Flutter for more that 1.5 years

Development in flutter is on the way.

I have mentored SIH2018, ACMWH2018 and SIH2019.

I am proud participant of SMART INDIA HACKATHON (World's biggest hackathon).

Project for the hackathon was automation in preparation of the tender document. The project was completed in 36 hours. It was held on the 1st of April.

# Experience

Rirev Flutter Dev May 2019 - Present Mumbai Area, India

Flutter Dev @ Rirev

StringsWay Tech Fluttter Developer February 2018 - Present Mumbai, Maharashtra, India Flutter Mumbai Organizer December 2019 - Present

Mumbai Area, India

ICICI Lombard
Flutter Developer Consultant
May 2019 - December 2019 (8 months)
Mumbai Area, India

Worked as flutter developer to build apps on Android and iOS for insurance domain

FitPhilia Solutions Private Limited Software Engineer August 2017 - May 2019 (1 year 10 months) Andheri

IlexSquare
Python Developer
July 2017 - August 2017 (2 months)
Mumbai, Maharashtra, India

I was here as a python developer.

bebitz flanges
IT intern
August 2016 - September 2016 (2 months)
ERP software learner

### Education

Haji Jamaluddin Thim TrustTheem College of Engineering B.E., Computer Engineering (2013 - 2017)

New English School 12th, HSC with computer Science

Pancham English High School 10th, SSC